Brenno Lima

Toronto, Ontario | 437 982 2579 | brennocesar@live.com | linkedin.com/in/brennocesarlima

OBJECTIVE

Obtain a **full time** employment as a **frontend Engineer** aiming professional and personal development.

ABOUT

As a front-end-focused web developer, I specialize in **UI/UX** design, **Javascript**, **React**, HTML, and CSS. My passion is creating beautiful and intuitive designs and bringing them to life. I have experience working with both big and small companies, and as a startup developer, I learned to be versatile and wear multiple hats. I have a strong learning ability and a positive attitude, always excited to take on new challenges and expand my skill set.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer - Igloo Software - Kitchener, ON.

2022 - current

- Developed and maintained interfaces using JavaScript, React, and TypeScript
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams for project success
- Designed and created user-friendly components with Figma
- Debugged, tested, and reviewed code to ensure high quality
- Proficient in React.js, JavaScript, UI/UX, TypeScript, Remix, Jira, and GitHub.

Frontend Developer - RecruitForMe Inc - Toronto, ON.

2022 - 2022

- Led frontend development for the entire application
- Designed and planned components using Figma
- Managed frontend interns, delegating tasks and reviewing code
- Proficient in Javascript, React, HTML, and CSS

Programmer Analyst - Cognizant - Toronto, ON.

2019 - 2020

• More details on LinkedIn.

SKILLS

Languages

• Javascript, TypeScript, Java, Python

UI/UX*

· React, Redux, Material UI, HTML, CSS, Tailwind, GSAP, Figma

Backend

GraphQL, Node, Express

Databases

· MongoDB, Oracle, SQL

QA

Manual Test, Automation Test

Tools

• GIT, Jira, VS Code, Unix, Postman

RECENT PROJECTS

Assessments - Interview challenges

Live link
GitHub code

Animated portfolio - Desktop only

• <u>Live link</u> • <u>GitHub code</u>

EDUCATION

Computer Programmer - Seneca College | Toronto, ON

2017 - 2019

• With honors (GPA 3.6)

Interested in learning more about me?

• Check my LinkedIn.